QUIZ_QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: 'Whats the capital of Australia?',
        answers: [
        "Canberra", "Melbourne", "Sydney", "Adelaide"
        ],
        correct: "Canberra"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of the USA?",
        answers: [
            "Washington DC", "New York", "Boston", "LA"
        ],
        correct: "Washington DC"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Brazil?",
        answers: [
            "Brasilia", "Sao Paulo", "Rio de Janeiro", "Recife"
        ],
        correct: "Brasilia"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Canada?",
        answers: [
            "Ottawa", "Toronto", "Vancouver", "Montreal"
        ],
        correct: "Ottawa"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of the Netherlands?",
        answers: [
            "Amsterdam", "The Hague", "Rotterdam", "Copenhagen"
        ],
        correct: "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Colombia?",
        answers: [
            "Bogota", "Medellin", "Cartagena","Cali"
        ],
        correct: "Bogota"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Afghanistan?",
        answers: [
            "Kabul", "Baghdad", "Kandahar", "Kunduz"
        ],
        correct: "Kabul"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Tajikistan?",
        answers: [
            "Dushanbe", "Samarkand", "Moscow", "Tashkent"
        ],
        correct: "Dushanbe"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Thailand?",
        answers: [
            "Bangkok", "Chiang Mai", "Kuala Lumpur", "Pai"
        ],
        correct: "Bangkok"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Spain?",
        answers: [
            "Madrid", "Barcelona", "Valencia", "Granada"
        ],
        correct: "Madrid"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Portugal?",
        answers: [
            "Lisbon", "Porto", "Faro", "Lagos"
        ],
        correct: "Lisbon"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Morocco?",
        answers: [
            "Rabat", "Marrakesh", "Casablanca", "Fes"
        ],
        correct: "Rabat"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Egypt?",
        answers: [
            "Cairo", "Alexandria", "Luxor", "Aswan"
        ],
        correct: "Cairo"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Egypt?",
        answers: [
            "Cairo", "Alexandria", "Luxor", "Aswan"
        ],
        correct: "Cairo"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Iran?",
        answers: [
            "Tehran", "Shiraz", "Isfahan", "Tabriz"
        ],
        correct: "Tehran"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Oman?",
        answers: [
            "Muscat", "Salalah", "Dubai", "Sohar"
        ],
        correct: "Muscat"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Kenya?",
        answers: [
            "Nairobi", "Mombasa", "Malindi", "Dar es Salaam"
        ],
        correct: "Nairobi"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of India?",
        answers: [
            "New Delhi", "Mumbai", "Jaipur", "Bangalore"
        ],
        correct: "New Delhi"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Argentina?",
        answers: [
            "Buenos Aires", "Cordoba", "Rosario", "Santiago"
        ],
        correct: "Buenos Aires"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Namibia?",
        answers: [
            "Windhoek", "Namib", "Cape Town", "Swakopmund"
        ],
        correct: "Windhoek"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Philippines?",
        answers: [
            "Manila", "Quezon City", "Cebu", "Boracay"
        ],
        correct: "Manila"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Serbia?",
        answers: [
            "Belgrade", "Novi Sad", "Zagreb", "Sarajevo"
        ],
        correct: "Belgrade"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the capital of Scotland?",
        answers: [
            "Edinburgh", "Glasgow", "Aberdeen", "Dundee"
        ],
        correct: "Edinburgh"
    },
]